123franchising.com 2013-06-13

# Privacy Policy | 123 Franchising UK

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy.  This privacy policy relates to the use of any personal information you provide to us through 123franchising.com.  
By accepting the privacy policy and the Terms and Conditions during registration or the sending of an enquiry, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.  
**  
Personal Information**  
You can view all of the content on our website without providing any personal information, however if you wish to seek additional information regarding a franchise opportunity, your personal details will be requested.  
The information you submit via our enquiry forms are only shared with the companies that you request information from.  
123franchising.com does not share, sell or trade your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes, unless authorised by you, however our sales representatives may contact you from time to time with any relevant offers or opportunities.  
**  
Submit Your Enquiry Form**  
When you submit an enquiry form for more information from one of our advertisers, your contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail, etc.) on the enquiry form, will be passed only to the businesses that you specify. No other business receives your contact information. Your information, however, is often stored in the receiving company’s database, as well as ours. Collected data may be stored in a database outside your home country.

**Franchise Matching Service**  
123 Franchising offers a Free Franchise Matching Service. We do our utmost to ensure the results from this service is as accurate as possible based upon the information you provide. 123 Franchising cannot guarantee the accuracy of claims made by franchisors in this matching process or the information franchisors provide you with. By using this Franchise Matching Service, you agree to be contacted by the franchisors suggested for you. 123 Franchising strongly recommends that you seek professional advice before making a decision on purchasing a franchise. Your information provided to us via the Franchise Matching Service will never be passed onto any third party. 

**Franchise Special Offers**  
'Special Offers' are sometimes provided by Franchises on the website. 123 Franchising shall not be liable for the information provided by these Franchises and the accuracy of these 'Special Offers.'   
**  
Cookies**  
We may collect non-personal information from your computer using cookies.  We use the collected information for site, analytical and marketing purposes.  It is not linked to any personal information  
In order to provide you with a better user experience, we ask that you do not set your browser to reject cookies.  
**  
Testimonials**  
Customer testimonials are often posted to our website which may contain personally identifiable information such as their name and location; however we always obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial.  
**  
Newsletter**  
You will only be added to our newsletter mailing list if you register to receive it. Your personal information will never be shared with any third parties. If you wish to unsubscribe from the mailing list, you may opt out by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link on our emails.  
**  
Links to other sites**  
We may provide links to other companies from our site.  
Once you leave and enter another site, you are subject to their privacy policies, and therefore we advise you to review their privacy policies before use.  
**  
Children's Privacy**  
123 Franchising is intended to be used by individuals over the age of 18. We do not seek or willingly collect information on children under the age of 18. If we discover that we have collected information of an individual under the age of 18, then we will remove that information from our system.  
**  
Security**  
While no data transfer can be completely secure, we will make reasonable efforts to secure your data while being transferred, stored or processed. We also use strict procedures within our organisation to ensure that all personal data are kept secure.  
**  
Updated Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy at any reason. Any modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting on the website, unless otherwise indicated. We encourage you to check back regularly and review this policy.  
**  
Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

View our [Terms & Conditions](http://123franchising.com/terms-and-conditions)
